Shreyansh Malewar

Pune (M.H) – 8226071537 – Shreyanshmalewar@gmail.com

About

A beginner developer with an experience of working in an organization with diverse people and being a part of team where I contributed to make a live project and made sure that I fulfill the role of a group member and meet customer needs.

Technical skills

Developing and Designing Web Pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.

Core Java Programming on Servers, JSP and MySQL databases.

Programming in C & C++ with Fundamentals of data Communication

Networks.

Soft - Skills

Confident, articulate, and professional speaking abilities.

Empathic listener and persuasive speaker.

Combine patience, determination, and persistence to troubleshoot organizational demands and client issues.

Education

Bachelor Of Technology in Computer Science

2018 - 2022

Amity University Raipur Chhattisgarh

Aggregate CGPA – 8

Experience

Leap Academy

10 may 2021 – 28 august 2021

Prodevans Technologies & Red Hat academy, Bengaluru, Karnataka.

Student Intern

learned basics to intermediate of Red Hat, python with GUI, OOP, also covered basics to intermediate of AWS (amazon web services) & made a live project.

Edgate Technologies

20 may 2020 – 28 June 2020

Texas Instruments, Bangalore, Karnataka.

Student Intern

A complete walk through of Advanced Embedded System Design using Tiva C series Microcontroller also learned to design an android application for an embedded or IOT system.

Additional Information

Consequently 2-year intercollege football championship winner.

Intermediate mountain and road Cyclist for 5 years.